Guide to the Beecher Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Diaries, Journals, & Notebooks, 1831-1939; Series III; 2' 81/2" (7 boxes)
  The materials in this series are arranged alphabetically by the name of the family member and chronologically under each name.
  - Beecher, Eunice White (Bullard)
    - Account of Wedding Trip, [1837] (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Beecher, Henry Ward
    - Diaries (1831-1858)
      - Diary fragment, re: Mother's letters, 1831 September 3 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - "Journal of Events, Feelings, Thoughts, Plans and C...Begun June 1835 at Lane Theology Seminary" [includes literary extracts and agricultural horticultural records], 1835-1839 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Journal fragment with promissory note of Talbot Bullard on verso, [1837] September 25 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Diary fragment, [ca.1835-1839] (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Diary, 1837-1855, 1858 (Box 70, Folder 6-8)
      - Diary, 1860-1864, [1872-1873] (Box 71, Folder 9-14)
    - Notebooks
      - Notebook, sermons (Feb 11-Nov 10, 1838) (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Notebook, list of members of the second Presbyterian Church, Indianapolis and partial list of the Plymouth Church members, 1838-ca.1850 (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - Notebook, mostly horticultural extracts and records, 1841 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - "Record of Times and Places of Preaching", 1841 (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - "Editorial Agricultural Book begun Jan 10, 1845" (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - "Hints and Indications of Plans of Sermons", 1848 (Box 71, Folder 20)
      - Diary Entries. Sermon Topics, 1849-1858 (Box 71, Folder 21)
      - Sermon outlines and notes, [c. 1855] (Box 71, Folder 22)
      - Notebook, 1863 (Box 72, Folder 23)
      - Sermon and lecture outlines, 1868 (Box 72, Folder 24)
      - Notebook "No. 1" on evolution, [1880's] (Box 72, Folder 25)
      - Notebook "No. 2" Thoughts on Evolution sermon topics, miscellaneous, [1880's] (Box 72, Folder 26)
      - Lecture topics, notes on trees and shrubs, undated (Box 72, Folder 27)
      - Sermon and lecture topics, undated (Box 72, Folder 28)
      - Sermon and lecture plans and summary of key events in his life, 1837-1873., undated (Box 72, Folder 29)
      - Notebook, miscellaneous, (1853?) (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Beecher, William C.
    - Florida Journal, 1871 (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - Diary, 1886 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Scoville, Annie (Beecher)
    - Account Book, address book, 1889 (Box 72, Folder 33)
    - Address books (Box 72, Folder 34)
    - Address Book (Box 73, Folder 35)
    - Appointment calendar, 1916, 1917, 1918 (Box 73, Folder 36)
    - Calendar of engagements, 1909 (Box 73, Folder 37)
    - Datebooks, 1889-1890, 1939 (Box 73, Folder 38)
    - Diary, 1875, 1890 (Box 73, Folder 39-40)
    - Lessonbook (Box 73, Folder 41)
    - Lessonbook, Natural History (Box 73, Folder 42)
    - Notebook, 1839, 1890 (Box 74, Folder 43-46)
    - Notebooks (Box 74, Folder 47)
    - Notebook on Birds, 1889 (Box 74, Folder 48)
    - Notebook, Greek lessons and letters, 1882-1883 (Box 75, Folder 49)
    - Notebook, lectures (Box 75, Folder 50)
    - Notebook, "The Schools", lectures on philosophy (Box 75, Folder 51)
    - Notebook, "Nannie's Sea Thoughts", Reminiscences of Travel (Box 75, Folder 52)
    - Notebook, reading notes (Box 75, Folder 53)
    - Notebooks, "Twelfth Night" (Box 75, Folder 54)
  - Scoville, Harriet E. (Beecher)
    - Commonplace book, undated (Box 75, Folder 55)
    - Diary, 1859-1860 (Box 75, Folder 56)
    - Diaries, 1864-1867 (Box 75, Folder 57)
    - Diaries, 1868-1871, 1877, 1879 (Box 76, Folder 58-59)
    - Letterbook, 1888-1891 (Box 76, Folder 60)
  - Scoville, Rev. Samuel
    - Book listing, names of friends (Box 76, Folder 61)
    - Diary, 1872, 1901-1902 (Box 76, Folder 62-63)
    - Letterbook, 1893-1902 (Box 76, Folder 64)
    - Notebook-"Review of Prof. Hitchcocks Lectures on Church History" (Box 76, Folder 65)
    - "Notes Upon My Little Place In The Country" (Box 76, Folder 66)
- Subject File, 1706-1818, 1830-1948; Series IV; 3' 9" (11 boxes)
  The SUBJECT FILE consists of correspondence, newspaper clippings, articles, letters, postcards, pamphlets and tracts, resolutions, maps, photographs, drawings and other materials which pertain both to the lives of various Beecher-Scoville family members and to the events and organizations with which they were associated. Personal materials pertaining to individual family members and family groups are arranged alphabetically under the subsection "Beecher-Scoville Family". Other subsections, however, may be related to the life of a particular family member. Thus "Hampton Institute" and "Indians" are associated with Annie B. Scoville; "Paxton Hibben", "Plymouth Church", and the "Tilton Scandal" are associated with Henry Ward Beecher.
  The SUBJECT FILE is divided as follows:
  Amistad Case
  Beecher-Scoville Family
  Bates, Katharine Lee
  Beecher Family
  Beecher, Catherine Ester
  Beecher, Charles
  Beecher, Eunice White (Bullard)
  Beecher, Henry Ward
  Beecher, Herbert Foote
  Beecher, Lyman
  Foote and Ward Families
  Rogers, Edward (1735-1813)
  Scoville Family
  Scoville, Harriet E. (Beecher)
  Scoville, Rev. Samuel
  Scoville, Samuel Jr.
  Stowe, Harriet Elisabeth Beecher
  Civil War
  Hampton Institute
  Indians
  National Indian Association
  Progressive Indian Association
  Photographs and Drawings
  Maps
  U. S. Department of Interior
  Writings about Indians
  Paxton Hibben
  Phrenology
  Plymouth Church
  The Building
  Programs and Publications
  Stamford, Ct.
  Tilton Scandal
  (Chronological order)
  - Amistad Case
    - Letter: Orin Fowler to unidentified re: Aid for the Amistad Captives, 1840 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Beecher-Scoville Family
    - Bates, Katherine Lee
      - Account of the illness and death of Katherine Lee Bates, [Katherine Coman] (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Service, 1929 May 12 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Clippings & memorabilia (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Beecher Family
      - Clippings, 1877-1900, undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Beecher, Katherine Esther
      - Clippings, 1924 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Beecher, Charles
      - Clippings, 1863 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Beecher, Eunice White (Bullard)
      - Clippings, 1878-1897 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Beecher, Henry Ward
      - Autobiographical notes (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Biographical: letters and manuscripts, 1848, 1855 (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Biographical: "Henry Ward Beecher", S. Parkes Cadman, undated (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Biographical: Personal Recollections of Henry Ward Beecher, James L. Corning, Sr., 1903 (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Biographical: "Memorial Address" Rev. David Otis Mears, 1887 (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - Biographical: Henry Ward Beecher, Rev. Joseph Parker, 1887 (Box 77, Folder 14)
      - Biographical: The Celebrated Henry Ward Beecher Letters, J.A. Serman, undated (Box 77, Folder 15)
      - Clippings - anecdotes (Box 77, Folder 16)
      - Clippings - re: biographies of Henry Ward Beecher (Box 77, Folder 17)
      - Clippings - Death of H.W.B., 1887 (Box 77, Folder 18-21)
      - Clippings - The Tilton Scandal - Folio 3, 1875 (Box 77, Folder 21a)
      - Clippings - Evolution, 1882-1886 (Box 77, Folder 22)
      - Clippings - miscellaneous (Box 77, Folder 23-25)
      - Clippings - Political views (Box 77, Folder 26)
      - Clippings - Religious views (Box 77, Folder 27)
      - Copies of poems [in H.W.B.'s hand] (Box 77, Folder 28)
      - Eulogies and Tributes, manuscripts, 1887 (Box 77, Folder 29)
      - Eulogies and tributes, printed, 1887-1888 (Box 78, Folder 30)
      - "A Greylock Pulpit", E.W.B. Memorial address author unknown, 1897 (Box 78, Folder 31)
      - Henry Ward Beecher; A Memorial, 1887 (Box 78, Folder 32)
      - "Notes on Mr. Beecher's Visit, Jan 19, 1871" by Emily (Merwine) Drury (Box 78, Folder 33)
      - Poems and Tributes, 1887 (Box 78, Folder 34)
      - Scrapbook clippings (Box 78, Folder 35)
    - Beecher, Herbert Foote
      - Clippings (Box 78, Folder 36)
    - Beecher, Lyman
      - Clippings and biographical sketch, 1830,1835,1893 (Box 78, Folder 37)
    - Beecher, Thomas K. - Clippings, 1870-1901 (Box 78, Folder 37a)
    - Foote and Ward Families
      - Foote genealogy, [post-1857] (Box 78, Folder 38)
      - Ward genealogy, 1835 (Box 78, Folder 38)
      - Copy of the will of Andrew Ward (1727-1799), undated (Box 78, Folder 38)
      - Deeds, 1706, 1734-1738, 1756-1757, 1770, 1782-1806 (Box 78, Folder 39)
      - Printed list of nominees to the Connecticut General Assembly, 1773 (Box 78, Folder 40)
      - Peter Vandervoort: bill for inspecting barrels of potash, 1774 (Box 78, Folder 40a)
      - Roxana Foote: bill for household goods, 1799 (Box 78, Folder 40a)
      - Herman Swift, Jr.: List of taxable property, 1800 (Box 78, Folder 40a)
      - Facsimile of the first issue of the Boston News-Letter, undated (Box 78, Folder 40a)
    - Rogers, Edward (1735-1813)
      - Subscription list and specifications for a schoolhouse in Cornwall, Ct., 1763 (Box 78, Folder 41)
      - List of taxables in Cornwall, Ct., 1763 (Box 78, Folder 41)
      - Personal and official papers, 1775-1793 (Box 78, Folder 41a)
      - Military papers, 1776-1777 (Box 78, Folder 41b)
      - Letter from his cousin [Prior?] Tanner, an early settler of Canfield, Ohio, [1805?] (Box 78, Folder 41c)
    - Scoville Family
      - "A Voyage with Captain Noah Scofield in the Ship Venus Bound to New York from London Docks", 1818 (Box 78, Folder 42)
      - -Foster: essay on the origin of the name, undated (Box 78, Folder 42)
    - Scoville, Harriet E. (Beecher)
      - Religious Tracts, undated (Box 79, Folder 43)
    - Scoville, Rev. Samuel
      - Clippings (Box 79, Folder 44)
      - Congregational Church, Stamford, Connecticut Miscellaneous printed matter, 1898, 1924 1945 (Box 79, Folder 45)
      - First Congregational Church, Norwich, New York, Miscellaneous printed Material, 1874, 1904 (Box 79, Folder 46)
      - Church matters (Box 79, Folder 47)
      - Contract between John Zundel, Samuel Scoville and Horatio C. King for publication of a hymnbook, 1873 May 6 (Box 79, Folder 48)
      - Inslee, Gage; poem commemorating the Scoville's 25th Wedding Anniversary, 1886 September 25 (Box 79, Folder 49)
      - Memorabilia (Box 79, Folder 50)
      - Memorials, 1922 (Box 79, Folder 51)
      - Memoranda, undated (Box 79, Folder 52)
      - Plan of Samuel Scoville's Stamford, Ct. House, by W.W. Kent (Box 79, Folder 53)
      - Samuel Scoville Associates Cornwall, Connecticut, 1926, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 54)
    - Scoville, Samuel
      - Sunday School Materials (Box 79, Folder 55)
      - "Tribute to Rev. Samuel Scoville" [from the Chenango Union, Oct 23, 1879] 2 copies (Box 79, Folder 56)
      - Volunteer Fire Department, honoring Samuel Scoville, 1874 April 15 (Box 79, Folder 57)
    - Scoville, Samuel Jr.
      - Clippings, undated (Box 79, Folder 58)
    - Stowe, Harriet E. (Beecher)
      - Clippings (Box 79, Folder 59)
      - Illustrations from Crusader in Crinoline by Forrest Wilson (Box 79, Folder 60)
  - Civil War
    - "Copy of Resolutions Passed Unanimously by the Members of the American Emigrant Company", 1865 November (Box 79, Folder 61)
    - Scofield, Sylvester L., Discharge from U.S. Army, 28th Conn. Vols., 1863 (Box 79, Folder 62)
    - Terms of enlistment in Colonel Olmsted's Zocave Company (Box 79, Folder 63)
    - Transcript of an interview between "Persons of African Descent and Edwin M. Stanton and Major General [William T.] Sherman, 1865 January 12 (Box 79, Folder 64)
    - Maps - Troop Movements - Cold Harbor to Petersburg; Grant's Campaign (Box 79, Folder 65)
  - Hampton Institute
    See also: Box 82, Folder 110 Box 82, Folder 122
    - Letter-Frazier, George J. "To the Boys of [The] Wigwam", 1895 (Box 80, Folder 66)
    - Letter- Southern Workman to: Hailman, William N., 1898 (Box 80, Folder 67)
    - Letters - To A Hampton Student, 1894 (Box 80, Folder 68)
    - Letters - Cornelius, Elisabeth L. to: Merrill, 1900 (Box 80, Folder 69)
    - Organization and Purpose
      - Fundraising: Circulars and appeals (Box 80, Folder 70)
      - Fundraising: Donation cards (Box 80, Folder 71)
      - The Halifax Plan For The Practical Education Of The Negro, [J.W. Church], 1910 (Box 80, Folder 72)
      - Hampton Institute Programs, 1893-1898 (Box 80, Folder 73)
      - "Hampton's Work For The Cabin and Camp," A.B. Scoville (Box 80, Folder 74)
      - "Indian Education At Hampton" - pamphlet (Box 80, Folder 75)
      - A.B. Scoville - list of her students from the Junior class of 1893-1894 and 1896-1897; "Golden Texts" (Box 80, Folder 76)
      - National Hampton Association Report, 1920 (Box 80, Folder 77)
      - "Rules of Life" of the self control alliance (Box 80, Folder 78)
      - A.B. Scoville, Sunday School records, 1892-1893 (Box 80, Folder 79)
      - A.B. Scoville "Work For [The] Negro at Hampton" (Box 80, Folder 80)
    - Student Expression
      - Thanksgiving day essays (unidentified), November 189- (Box 80, Folder 81)
      - Personal Mottoes and Resolves of Students (Box 80, Folder 82)
      - Humorous poem about photographing Indians (unidentified), undated (Box 80, Folder 83)
      - Ink Sketch of a warrior on verso of a printed program (Box 80, Folder 84)
      - Talks and Thoughts of The Hampton Indian Students, 1892-1893 (Box 80, Folder 85)
    - Photos
      - Hampton Institute Buildings (Box 80, Folder 86)
      - Hampton Institute Grounds and Buildings (Box 80, Folder 87)
      - Photographs - Scenes around Hampton, Va. (Box 80a, Folder 88)
      - Scenes near Hampton (Box 80a, Folder 89)
      - Hampton students group portraits (Box 80a, Folder 90)
      - Hampton Institute students, individual portraits (Box 80a, Folder 91)
      - Hampton Institute students (Box 80a, Folder 92-93)
      - Hampton Institute Teachers (Box 81, Folder 94-95)
      - Photographic Plates - Hampton Institute and vicinity (Box 81, Folder 96)
      - Hampton Institute Students (Box 81, Folder 97)
      - Postcards- Calhoun School and Settlement, Calhoun, Alabama (Box 81, Folder 98)
      - Postcards of Hampton Institute (Box 81, Folder 99)
      - Postcards and photograph- Penn School, St. Helena Island, S.C. (Box 81, Folder 100)
      - Postcards and Photographs of Southern Scenes (Box 81, Folder 101)
      - Postcards - Southern Scenes (Box 81, Folder 102)
      - Slides of Hampton Institute - Buildings, Classes, Activities (Box 81, Folder 103)
    - Related Materials
      - Hill, David Russell "American Lay" Celebrating Dawes Act, 1895, December (Box 81, Folder 104)
      - "The Church and Race Relations" - Federal Council of Churches, 1946. (Box 81, Folder 105)
      - Copy of James Weldon Johnson's Poem "Fifty Years - 1863-1913" (Box 81, Folder 106)
      - Fisk Jubilee Singers Flyer, 1882 (Box 81, Folder 107)
      - John Hopkins Colored Orphan Asylum List of Board of Visitors (Box 81, Folder 108)
      - Statement on Education in Macon County, [GA.?] (Box 81, Folder 109)
  - Indians
    - Government documents: Acts re: allotment and distribution of Indian lands, 1877, 1899 (Box 82, Folder 110)
    - Government documents: House Resolution re: Allotment and Distribution of Indian Tribal Funds, 1905-1906 (Box 82, Folder 111)
    - List of All Indian Treaties and Agreements (Box 82, Folder 112)
    - Indian Languages
      - "Notes on the Dakota Language as spoken by the Sioux at Santee Agency, Nebraska:, undated (Box 82, Folder 113)
      - "Omaha and Ponka Letters," by James Owen Dorsey, 1891 (Box 82, Folder 114)
      - Writings, miscellaneous (Box 82, Folder 115)
    - Indian Schools
      - The Oahe Industrial School (Box 82, Folder 116)
      - Santee Normal Training School, 1903-1904 (Box 82, Folder 117)
      - American Missionary Association, Correspondence (Box 82, Folder 118)
      - Indian Rights Association, Invitation to the 22nd Annual Meeting (Box 82, Folder 119)
      - Lake Mohonk Conference of Friends of the Indians Proceedings of the 18th Annual Meeting, 1900 (Box 82, Folder 120)
      - Lake Mohonk Conference of Friends of the Indians and Other Dependent Peoples, Partial program of 27th Annual Meeting (Box 82, Folder 121)
    - National Indian Association
      - National Indian Association, Account Book, 1885-1905 (Box 82, Folder 122)
      - N.I.A. Announcements for 1901, 1910 Annual Meetings (Box 82, Folder 123)
      - National Indian Association, Correspondence, 1886-1899, 1901-1909, undated (Box 82, Folder 124-130)
      - National Indian Association, Financial Papers and Deeds. (Box 82, Folder 131)
      - Official Pamphlet of the National Indian Association with Suggestions and Facts..., 1882 (Box 82, Folder 132)
      - "Our Industrial Work" National Indian Association Pamphlet, 1903 (Box 82, Folder 133)
      - National Indian Association Report of Home Building and Loan Committee, 1900 (Box 82, Folder 134)
      - Progressive Indian Association, Correspondence, 1909 (Box 82, Folder 135)
      - Sequoya League, Inc., Correspondence, 1902-1903 (Box 82, Folder 136)
    - Photographs and drawings
      - The Indian and His Solitude - A series of prints (Box 83, Folder 137)
      - Indian families and settlements in the West (Box 83, Folder 138-142)
      - Slides of Indians (Box 83, Folder 143)
      - Indian Students at Hampton, 1901 May 29 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - Indian Portraits (Box 83, Folder 144)
      - Sioux Indians S.O. (Box 83, Folder 144b)
    - Maps
      - Map of South Dakota (Box 84, Folder 145)
      - Indian tribes of Long Island and vicinity - Map (Box 84, Folder 146)
    - U.S. Department of Interior
      - Annual Report of the Board of Indian Commissioners, 1907, 1923 (Box 84, Folder 147)
      - Correspondence (Box 84, Folder 148)
      - Weekly Statement of Public Funds (Box 84, Folder 149)
      - Wo-Raw-Hay-Kaw Identification papers issued by Supt. of Indian Affairs (Box 84, Folder 150)
      - U.S. Department of Justice, Correspondence, 1905 (Box 84, Folder 151)
    - Writings About Indians
      - Garland, Hamlin, "General Custer's Last Fight As Seen By Two Moon" (Box 84, Folder 152)
      - Lowie, Robert H., Spinden, Herbert J., articles on Indian dances, The American Museum Journal, 1915, March (Box 84, Folder 153)
      - Hewett, Edgar L., "Native American Artists", Art and Archaeology XIII, 1922, March (Box 84, Folder 154)
      - The Basket, Vol. I, 1903 (Box 84, Folder 155)
      - Collins, Rev. Mary C., "Indian Womanhood", undated (Box 84, Folder 156)
      - Eggleston, Edward, "Indian Wars in the Colonies., 1883 (Box 84, Folder 157)
      - Foster, Maximillan, "The Survivors: A Tale of the Last Bison Herd", undated (Box 84, Folder 158)
      - Gates, Merrill Edwards, "Land and Law as Agents in Educating Indians", undated (Box 84, Folder 159)
      - Grinnell, George B., "The Last of the Buffalo", Scribner's Magazine, XII, 1892 (Box 84, Folder 160)
      - Jones, W.A., "The Standing Rock Indian Case", 1902 (Box 84, Folder 161)
      - Kennan, George, "Have Reservation Indians Any Vested Rights?" Outlook, 1902 (Box 84, Folder 162)
      - Schell, Joseph, "Reasons for Revisions of Indian Land Allotments,", undated (Box 84, Folder 163)
      - Scoville, Annie Beecher, "Ezuzu", undated (Box 84, Folder 164)
      - Scoville, Annie Beecher, Notes on Indians, undated (Box 84, Folder 165)
      - Scoville, Annie Beecher, "Have You Known it All This Time and Never Told Us?", undated (Box 84, Folder 166)
      - Wilson, Gilbert, "The American Indians", poems selected from Myths of the Red Children, undated (Box 84, Folder 167)
      - Broadsides, 1888 (Box 84, Folder 168)
      - "The Church's Mission to the Outsiders" (unknown author), 1899 (Box 84, Folder 169)
      - "Concerted International Restraint of the Traffic in Intoxicants and Opium Among Aboriginal Races", International Reform Bureau, [1909] (Box 84, Folder 170)
      - "Dancing for Fire Cloud", author unknown, undated (Box 84, Folder 171)
      - Howe, Guy, Indian School letter, 1896 (Box 84, Folder 171a)
      - "An Indian's View of Indian Affairs - What Chief John Cannot Understand", undated (Box 84, Folder 172)
      - "Manuel Training for Indians", undated (Box 84, Folder 173)
      - Miscellaneous Writings, 1925, undated (Box 84, Folder 174)
      - A Neglected People, pamphlet, 1908 (Box 84, Folder 175)
      - Newsclippings, 1906 (Box 84, Folder 176)
      - Speech about (author unknown), 1904 (Box 84, Folder 177)
      - "The Spider, the Panther, and the Shake," [Indian fairy tale published by the Indian students of Hampton Institute., 1893 (Box 84, Folder 178)
      - "Statistics of Indian Tribes, Agencies, and Schools", 1899 (Box 84, Folder 179)
      - "White Breast's Epic of the Winnebago", undated (Box 84, Folder 180)
      - "A Woman's Way" (author unknown), undated (Box 84, Folder 181)
  - Hibben, Paxton
    - Paxton Hibben Clippings, 1927-1928 (Box 85, Folder 182)
    - Henry Ward Beecher, An American Portrait, clippings, 1927-1928, 1942 (Box 85, Folder 183)
    - Henry Ward Beecher, An American Portrait, Xerox copies of clippings, 1927-1928 (Box 85, Folder 184)
    - Notes on Hibben by Annie Beecher Scoville (Box 85, Folder 185)
    - Copy of Hibben's book annotated by Annie Beecher Scoville, (1927) (Box 85, Folder 186)
    - Annie Beecher Scoville's Criticism of Hibbin's book, 1928 (Box 85, Folder 187)
    - "Synopsis of Phrenology; and the Phrenological Developments...", 1841 (Box 85, Folder 188)
    - Fowler, L.N., Phrenological Character reading of S.I.M. Merwin (Box 85, Folder 189)
  - Plymouth Church
    - Designs for Plymouth Church Building (Box 86, Folder 190)
    - "Statement of the Trustees of Plymouth Church of Architects", 1859 April 4 (Box 86, Folder 191)
    - Pews Rented in Plymouth Church - Henry C. Bowen, Treasurer (Box 86, Folder 192)
    - Plan of Pews, with rents, 1883 (Box 86, Folder 193)
    - Unveiling of the Windows of Plymouth Church, December 29, 1907 (Box 86, Folder 194)
    - Programs and Publications
      - Henry Ward Beecher Memorial Services, 1888, 1891 (Box 86, Folder 195)
      - Henry Ward Beecher, Plymouth Silver Wedding Anthem, 1872 (Box 86, Folder 196)
      - Plymouth Chimes, 1911 September (Box 86, Folder 197)
      - Plymouth Church Clippings, 1872-1905, undated (Box 86, Folder 198)
      - Plymouth Church Fair Record, (1887?) (Box 86, Folder 199)
      - Hymnal Supplement for Use in Plymouth Church, 1880 (Box 86, Folder 200)
      - Plymouth Church, Brooklyn, printed notices, 1872 (Box 86, Folder 201)
      - Proceedings of a Council for the Installation of Rev, Lyman Abbott, 1890 (Box 86, Folder 202)
      - Plymouth Church, programs, 1904, 1924 (Box 86, Folder 203)
      - Program of a "Greate Concerte" 1873 for The Benefit of Plymouth Church (Box 86, Folder 204)
      - "The Life of Isaac: A Series of Tableaux. Prepared for Plymouth Sunday School, 1871 (Box 86, Folder 205)
      - List of Brooklyn Clergyman (Box 86, Folder 206)
  - Stamford
    - Stamford, Ct. "Food in early Stamford", undated (Box 87, Folder 207)
    - Stamford, Ct., King's Highway Letter from A.C. Arnold to (Mrs.) Squire, 1915 December 18 (Box 87, Folder 208)
    - Minutes of Stamford Historical Society, 1914 February 27 (Box 87, Folder 209)
  - Tilton Scandal
    - Henry Ward Beecher's notes on the rupture with Tilton and the beginnings of the scandal, 1870-1871 (Box 87, Folder 210)
    - Henry Ward Beecher Memoranda on Tilton Scandal (Box 87, Folder 211-212)
    - Copy of a letter from Theodore Tilton to Samuel E. Belcher, 1873 [October 31] (Box 87, Folder 213)
    - Account of a meeting of the Clinton Avenue Church to debate the question of disciplining Plymouth Church [pp. 1-8 missing], [1813] (Box 87, Folder 214)
    - Plymouth Church, special meeting notes by E. Beecher, 1873 November 26 (Box 87, Folder 215)